phreephuck.com 2017-04-02

# Privacy Policy | PH Reep Huck

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains the data practices of Phreephuck.com (“Phreephuck.com”, “us”, or “we”). As a general description of our services, Phreephuck.com is a hosted advertising management platform that provides targeted advertisement insertion and scheduling, campaign management and reporting on a real-time basis primarily used in the monetization of online video content. Part I of this Privacy Policy describes our data practices with respect to information we collect about our customers and other visitors to the Website (“Customers”), while Part II describes our data practices with respect to information collected by our Customers using Phreephuck.com’s ad serving services. The general provisions in Part III apply to our data practices in both Part I and Part II.

As used in this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means information about you that is personally identifiable to you, such as your name, address, email address, phone numbers, or credit card number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. “Anonymous Information” means information that cannot identify a particular person.

Phreephuck.com respects your privacy. Visit our AdChoices page to learn about online behavorial advertising, and what you can do to opt-out of receiving behaviorally targeted ads.

**Part I**

**Customer-Provided Information**

This Part I describes Phreephuck.com’s use of Personal Information and Anonymous Information that we collect when you or your representative use our Services. By visiting the Phreephuck.com website, and/or using our service (the Website and services we offer are collectively referred to as the “Services”), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. As used in this Part I, “you” and “your” refer to the employees or contractors of Phreephuck.com’s Customers.

  1. **COLLECTION OF CUSTOMER-PROVIDED INFORMATION**

The individuals who represent Phreephuck.com’s Customers or potential Customers (“Business Contacts”) may voluntarily provide their contact information and related data, including Personal Information, to Phreephuck.com by various means, including telephone, email, postal mail, comments, or other means. The Personal Information submitted to Phreephuck.com is used to communicate with and provide services for Customers. Phreephuck.com corrects or updates Personal Information when requested to do so by the applicable Business Contact.

When a Business Contact accesses reports through Phreephuck.com’s servers, or otherwise uses the Phreephuck.com platform, certain information may also be collected passively, including your Internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, and operation system. Phreephuck.com also stores a small text file called a cookie (“Cookie”) on your computer. Each Cookie has a unique identifier (“Cookie ID”) that enables us to recognize your login information and personalized settings. Phreephuck.com may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Phreephuck.com also uses Cookies, and other navigational data that is passively collected, to gather information about your visit to the Services and the information which you searched and viewed on the Services. Most browsers are initially set up to accept Cookies, but you may reset your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Services may not function properly if your Cookies are disabled.

We may receive Personal Information about you from other sources like telephone or fax, or from third-parties that provide services for us in connection with the Services. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via our Services.

  2. **USE OF CUSTOMER-PROVIDED INFORMATION**

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used by us either to register you for our Services, respond to requests that you make, communicate with the Customer for whom you work regarding the Services (including for invoicing purposes), to improve our Services and to better tailor the features, performance and support of the Services, and to offer you additional information, opportunities, and functionality. If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may provide Personal Information to third-parties to the extent such third-parties provide operational assistance (i.e., outsourced or third-party services) to Phreephuck.com and then only for that purpose. Examples of such third-party services include sending email, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. However, these service providers do not have any independent right to share this information (expect pursuant to a legal requirement such as a subpoena or warrant). Phreephuck.com may share some or all of your Personal Information with current or future Affiliates, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

Phreephuck.com may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. We may use this Anonymous Information to analyze usage patterns so that we may enhance our Services. We reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to third-parties in our discretion. This Anonymous Information may include, but is not limited to, browser type, URLs visited, and search terms entered.

**Part II**

**Ad-Serving Information**  
This Part II describes Phreephuck.com’s use of Personal Information and Anonymous Information that we collect in connection with the Phreephuck.com’s video advertisement serving technology. As used in this Part II, “you” and “your” refer to individuals who visit websites that use Phreephuck.com’s video advertisement serving technology (Network Sites). The collection, use and disclosure of information by Network Sites is governed by the privacy policies and practices of the Network Sites and their operators; Phreephuck.com does not control such policies and practices.

  1. **WHAT IS AD SERVING?**

In order to support valuable content without charging visitors, websites sell advertising space on their Web pages or within video content streamed on their Web pages. Companies like Phreephuck.com provide ads to websites and provide technology for website publishers and advertisers to display or to stream ads.

When you visit a website, your Internet browser transmits a “request” to that website’s server “asking” that server to send you the Web page that you are seeking. Most Web pages contain components that are pulled from different sources, for example, a Web page at a news site may get its weather section from one provider, its sports results from a different source, and advertisements from other servers.

If the website is a Network Site and is using Phreephuck.com’s technology to display ads on its site, the Web page will contain coding that directs your browser to fill the ad space on the Web page with content from one of Phreephuck.com’s ad servers. Phreephuck.com’s platform for streaming video ads enables advertisers to target their campaigns against particular contextual, geographic, interest or demographic criteria associated with the website or browser, and bid an amount they are willing to pay for this targeted impression. Each time a Network Site queries our platform for an advertisement, Phreephuck.com serves the most valuable advertisement to the publisher’s ad slot. Please note that Phreephuck.com does not control the privacy policies of the Network Sites, publishers and advertisers who use our services.

  2. **COLLECTION AND USE OF AD-SERVING INFORMATION**

Each Network Site includes video ad serving code on its website that enables Phreephuck.com to serve ads on the site and to place Phreephuck.com Cookies. Phreephuck.com Cookies are used to help manage ad delivery and frequency, and to identify audience segment(s) for customized advertising. Phreephuck.com does not collect or store any personal identification or sensitive information, such as your name, address, phone number, address, financial account information, social security numbers, or health information.

The video ads served may include instrumentation tags that enable Phreephuck.com to collect information about a person’s interaction with the ad for use in billing and analytical purposes. Each time one of Phreephuck.com’s servers receives a request for a video advertisement, Anonymous Information about the request is recorded for example, the date and time, the geographic location of the browser (based on IP address), the website and page to which the ad or image was delivered, any associated search terms, the Phreephuck.com Cookie ID, and the browser operating system. This information is used for reporting, analytical, modeling and targeting purposes, and also to better manage ad campaigns and the user experience, for example, to manage the number of times a particular user is exposed to the same advertisement.

Phreephuck.com may also make requests to multiple third-party data vendors for additional anonymous user audience information that is used for targeting, analytic and reporting purposes. No Personal Information is ever shared by Phreephuck.com with its third-party data vendors, although the third-party data vendors may provide Phreephuck.com with Anonymous Information that can be merged with existing Anonymous Information. Phreephuck.com only works with third-party data vendors who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) which sets the industry’s standards for online privacy accountability.

Phreephuck.com also works with approved affiliates for the collection and aggregation of search terms used for audience modeling and targeting purposes. No Personal Information is ever shared by Phreephuck.com with these affiliates, but Phreephuck.com may share aggregate Anonymous Information with these affiliates. Phreephuck.com may retain and target keyword category associations for up to 30 days.

**Part III**

**General Provisions**

As used in this Part III, “you” and “your” refer to both Phreephuck.com’s Customers and individuals who visit websites using Phreephuck.com’s video advertisement serving technology.

  1. **SECURITY AND CONFIDENTIALITY**

Phreephuck.com has put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and organizational procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, no company, including Phreephuck.com, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

We may disclose Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of us, the visitors and users of our Services, or third parties.

  2. **SUCCESSORS**

In the event Phreephuck.com goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred or assigned. You acknowledge that such transfers or assignment may occur, and that any acquirer of Phreephuck.com, or of all or a portion of its assets, may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. You hereby consent to Phreephuck.com sharing your Personal Information under the above circumstances.

  3. **CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes to it we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, the Website, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what Personal Information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

  4. **QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us here. This Privacy Policy was last updated in September 2016.
